Sorry
I'm not forcing you to accept this name
I saw the report
Starting today
Fu Group will restore your heir status
Whether to make it public
And to what extent
Requires your personal consent
My conditions remain the same
Go ahead
First no releasing Su Mingyao's
past details from 15 years ago
She helped me back then
But it can't be used for public gossip
Rest assured Mrs Fu
Fu Group won't exploit this past
Second I'll cooperate with the restoration
But I won't move into the Fu house immediately
Okay
Third my marriage is not subject
to any internal discussions
You and Mrs Fu are legally registered
The Fu family respects that
Fu Chenzhou you don't need to shield me from everything
Just a habit